{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906193108","data":{"timestamp":" 946906193108"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 5fd41914-4967-43a9-9706-7390f62fbce9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zawadi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAWADI"," userResponse":" ZAWADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906202663","data":{"timestamp":" 946906202662"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 5fd41914-4967-43a9-9706-7390f62fbce9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zawadi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAWADI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906204287","data":{"timestamp":" 946906204286"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 5fd41914-4967-43a9-9706-7390f62fbce9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZI"," userResponse":" ZIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906217106","data":{"timestamp":" 946906217106"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 5fd41914-4967-43a9-9706-7390f62fbce9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZI"," userResponse":" ZIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906218712","data":{"timestamp":" 946906218712"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 5fd41914-4967-43a9-9706-7390f62fbce9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zabibu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZABIBU"," userResponse":" ZABIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906226449","data":{"timestamp":" 946906226449"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 5fd41914-4967-43a9-9706-7390f62fbce9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zabibu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZABIBU"," userResponse":" ZABIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906228051","data":{"timestamp":" 946906228051"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 5fd41914-4967-43a9-9706-7390f62fbce9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906233135","data":{"timestamp":" 946906233135"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 5fd41914-4967-43a9-9706-7390f62fbce9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906234707","data":{"timestamp":" 946906234707"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 5fd41914-4967-43a9-9706-7390f62fbce9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zeze"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZEZE"," userResponse":" ZEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906256488","data":{"timestamp":" 946906256488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 5fd41914-4967-43a9-9706-7390f62fbce9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zeze"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906256590","data":{"timestamp":" 946906256590"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 5fd41914-4967-43a9-9706-7390f62fbce9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zeze"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZEZE"," userResponse":" ZEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906312311","data":{"timestamp":" 946906312311"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_162938"," gameId":" 40df5958-a521-42d4-a5ac-3627e3760497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}